?THEME SONG: Are you ready, kids
主题曲：孩子们，准备好了吗
!Aye, aye, captain
！是啊是啊，队长
!I can't hear you
！我听不到你说话
!Aye, aye, captain
！是啊是啊，队长
Oh-- Who lives in a
?pineapple under the sea
哦——谁住在一个
?海底菠萝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Absorbent and yellow
.and porous is he
吸水性和黄色
.他是多孔的
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
If nautical nonsense
--be something you wish
如果航海废话
--成为你想要的东西
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
Then drop on the deck
.and flop like a fish
然后落在甲板上
.然后像鱼一样扑通扑通
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
?Ready
？准备好
!SpongeBob SquarePants
!海绵宝宝
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
NARRATOR: Ah, another
beautifully day
旁白：啊，另一个
美好的一天
in Bikini Bottom's
,own jellyfish fields
在比基尼泳裤的
,自己的水母田
an untamed world of
natural order, where
一个未驯服的世界
自然顺序，其中
the little jellyfish
jellies roam
小水母
果冻漫游
.free across the salty seascape
.自由地穿越咸咸的海景
And where there is
jellyfish, there
还有哪里有
水母，那里
.is is the jellyfish hunter
.is是水母猎人
.La, la, la, la la-
.啦啦啦啦-
.La, la la, la, la
.啦啦啦啦啦啦
You're my twelfth
.catch of the day
你是我的第十二个
.当天的渔获
.I'm going to call you Twelvie
.我要叫你Twelvie
!Cootchie cootchie coo
！咕咕咕咕
[LOUD SNEEZE]
[大声喷嚏]
!Bye, Twelvie
！再见，十二
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
[ELECTRIC CHARGE]
[电荷]
!Oh
！哦
!It's you
！是你
[THUMP]
[扑通]
Well, it's just
.you and me again
嗯，这只是
.你和我再次
I've caught and
named every jellyfish
我已经抓住了并且
为每只水母命名
in this field at least
.once, except you, No-Name
至少在这个领域
.曾经，除了你，无名之辈
[BUZZING TAUNT]
[嗡嗡的嘲讽]
!Blululululululululululu
！ 布鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁
!Blululululu
！布鲁鲁鲁鲁
[HEART BEATING]
[心跳]
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
!Blululululululululu
！布鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁鲁
!Gotcha
！明白了
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
!Barnacles
！藤壶
?How does he do that
？他是怎么做到的
.Someday I'll catch old No-Name
.总有一天我会抓住老无名氏
I'm going on my lunch
.break, Mr. Krabs
我要去吃午饭了
.break，蟹老板
.You got five minutes-
.你有五分钟时间-
!Wow-
！哇-
!One more minute than yesterday
！比昨天多了一分钟
!SpongeBob ready for launch
！海绵宝宝准备发射
[ROCKET NOISES]
[火箭噪音]
[GNAWING]
[啃咬]
!Yum
！嗯
!GULPING] Yeah]
！吞咽]是啊]
[GNAWING]
[啃咬]
Hey, Buddy, what-
?the heck is that
嘿，伙计，什么——
？到底是这样的
.Why, this is a hole, good sir-
.为什么，这是一个洞，好先生-
,You see, I am a sponge
--and we typically
，你看，我是一块海绵
——我们通常
.Not that-
.不是那个-
!That
！那
It's just a little-
old krabby patty
这只是一点点——
老蟹肉饼
.smothered in jellyfish jelly
.被水母果冻窒息
I call it a krabby patty
.with jellyfish jelly
我叫它蟹肉饼
.与水母果冻
?Could I try some-
？我可以尝试一些-
!Sure-
！当然-
[GULPING]
[吞咽]
!Amazing-
！惊人的-
I've got to tell
!someone about this
我必须告诉
!有人对此
!SINGING) Hey, all you people)
！唱歌）嘿，你们所有人）
!Hey, all you people
！嘿，你们所有人
Hey, all you people
?won't you listen to me
嘿，你们所有人
？你不听我说吗
,I just had a sandwich
.no ordinary sandwich
,我刚吃了一个三明治
A sandwich filled
!with jellyfish jelly
填满了三明治
!与水母果冻
Hey, man, you've got
.to try this sandwich
嘿，伙计，你有
.尝尝这个三明治
.It's no ordinary sandwich
.这不是普通的三明治
It's the tastiest
.sandwich in the sea
这是最好吃的
.海里的三明治
[SCAT SINGING]
[SCAT 唱歌]
[APPLAUSE]
[掌声]
.Heh, heh
.呵呵
!Thank you
！谢谢
SpongeBob, who's playing-
?Squidward's records again
海绵宝宝，谁在玩——
?章鱼哥再次记录
.No one, Mr. Krabs-
.没有人，蟹老板-
I was just sharing my jellyfish
.jelly with the customers
我只是分享我的水母
.jelly 与顾客
[GNAWING]
[啃咬]
.Here, Mr. Krabs
.这里，蟹老板先生
Send your taste
.buds on a journey
发送您的口味
.旅途中的芽
[SNIFFING]-
[嗅探]-
Messing with the
?patties' formula
搞乱
?肉饼的公式
!That's mutiny
！这就是叛变
--Why I ought to
——为什么我应该
Sir, this is the greatest-
.thing I've ever eaten
先生，这是最伟大的——
.我吃过的东西
I'm going to come back
here for lunch every day
我会回来的
每天都来这里吃午饭
.for the rest of my life
.在我的余生中
,CASH REGISTER DING] Hey]
?Buddy, you all right
,收银机叮]嘿嘿]
？哥们，你还好吧
[BLUBBERING]
[哭泣]
?You OK, Mr. K-
？你还好吧，K先生-
SpongeBob, I got a-
.proposition for you
海绵宝宝，我有一个——
.给你的建议
How's about you go catch me
.some of those little money fish
你去抓我怎么样
.一些小金钱鱼
!Oh boy-
！哦天哪-
,Getting paid to jellyfish
!that's my life's dream
,向水母付钱
！这是我一生的梦想
.Well, keep dreaming-
.好吧，继续梦想吧-
.This will be on your time
.这将是你的时间
!Aye, aye, sir-
！是啊，是啊，先生——
Now go get me some-
--jellyfish and make it
现在去给我拿一些——
--水母并制作它
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
.Quick --
。快的  -
,Uh, SpongeBob
we're going to need
，呃，海绵宝宝
我们需要
.more than one puny jellyfish
.不止一只微小的水母
But, sir, how many-
?jellyfish do you need
但是，先生，有多少——
？你需要水母吗
SpongeBob, we have
a whole ecosystem
海绵宝宝，我们有
整个生态系统
,full of hungry
.paying customers
,饱饱的
.付费客户
.Oh no
.哦不
.Don't tell me
.别告诉我
You've stopped caring
.for the customer
你已经不再关心
.为客户
.GASP] No]-
.GASP] 否]-
!Never
！绝不
Then go out there and-
!get me some more jellies
然后出去——
！再给我一些果冻
.OK, Mr. Krabs-
.好的，蟹老板-
Just make sure the
.jellyfish are comfortable
只需确保
.水母很舒服
.They are oh so sensitive
.他们太敏感了
.Oh-
。哦-
I'll keep them comfortable
.all right-- inside me wallet
我会让他们感到舒适
.好吧——在我的钱包里
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
[邪恶的笑声]
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
.Here you go, Mr. Krabs-
.给你，蟹老板先生-
I'm going to need-
!more than that, boy
我需要-
！不仅如此，男孩
.More jellies, Mr. Krabs-
.更多果冻，蟹老板-
.Oh, that will never do-
.哦，那永远不会-
!More
！更多的
!More, SpongeBob
！更多，海绵宝宝
[SQUEAKING WHEELS]
[吱吱作响的车轮]
What don't you
?understand about more
你不怎么办
?了解更多
!More
！更多的
.Well, there's no more-
.好吧，没有更多了-
!Now that's jellyfishing
！现在就是捕水母了
[HUMMING]
[嗡嗡声]
[BUZZING]
[HUMMING]
[嗡嗡声]
It feels like
(somebody (SHOUTING
感觉就像
（有人（大喊
!wants to sell me something
！想卖给我东西
[WIND GUSTS]
[阵风]
.I told you was on to us-
.我告诉过你我们正在关注-
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
SHOUTING) I'm not interested)-
!in anything you're selling
喊）我不感兴趣）-
!在你销售的任何东西中
[PANTING]
[气喘吁吁]
!Gee, it sure felt like-- bah
！哎呀，确实感觉就像——呸
.I must be working too hard
.一定是我工作太辛苦了
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[电话铃声]
!I'll get it, Gary
！我会得到它，加里
.Hello, SpongeBob's house
.你好，海绵宝宝的家
.SpongeBob speaking
.海绵宝宝说话
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[粗重的呼吸声]
?Hello-
？你好-
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[粗重的呼吸声]
[DIAL TONE]
[拨号音]
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]--
.Wrong number
[紧张的笑声]——
.号码错误
NERVOUS LAUGHTER] I]--
guess Gary forgot to pay
紧张的笑声]我]--
猜想加里忘了付钱
.the electric bill
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
.电费单
[紧张的笑声]
[CREAKING DOOR]
[吱吱作响的门]
?Gary-
？加里-
?Is that you
？那是你吗
!SHOUTING) Gary)
！大喊）加里）
.Uh, yeah, good idea, Gary
.呃，是的，好主意，加里
There's probably some
.candles in the kitchen
大概有一些
.厨房里的蜡烛
!Hello
！你好
?What's this
?这是什么
How did you get in
?here, oh delicious one
你是怎么进来的
？这里，哦，美味的
A little snack will
.calm my nerves
一点零食就会
.安抚我的神经
.Mmm
.嗯
.A krabby patty with blue jelly
.蓝色果冻蟹肉饼
!Aah
！啊啊
?SCREAMING) Blue jelly)
？尖叫）蓝色果冻）
.PANICKY) Hello, No-Name)
.PANICKY）你好，无名）
?What's happening
?发生了什么事
.MUFFLED) No-Name, let me out)
.MUFFLED）无名，让我出去）
What are you going
?to do with me
你要去做什么
？与我有关
.PU
?What smells like big business
？什么闻起来像大生意
Hey, I don't remember
.that factory
嘿，我不记得了
.那个工厂
?Huh
？哈
!Ah
！啊
?What is this horrible place
？这是什么可怕的地方
(ROBOTIC VOICE)
.Cootchie cootchie coo
（机器人声音）
.咕咕咕咕
What kind of monster is-
?responsible for this horror
是什么样的怪物——
？对这起恐怖事件负责
.That's it, boys-
.就是这样，孩子们-
Keep that gelatinous
.gold a' flowing
保持凝胶状
.gold a' 流动
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
?Mr. Krabs-
？先生。蟹蟹-
!No
！不
Now I know why you
.brought me here
现在我知道你为什么
.把我带到这里
?But what can we do
？但是我们能做什么
[DANCE MUSIC]
[舞曲]
!Mr. Krabs-
！先生。蟹蟹-
!Stop this madness
！停止这种疯狂行为
!Stop it right now
！立即停止
Hey, hey, hey-- this isn't-
.what it looks like, SpongeBob
嘿嘿嘿——这不是——
.它看起来像什么，海绵宝宝
,Why, uh, we're just, uh, uh
.having a little tea party
，为什么，呃，我们只是，呃，呃
.举办一个小型茶会
!Oh boy, a tea party-
！哦天哪，茶会-
[BUZZING]
[嗡嗡声]
.You tricked me, Mr. Krabs
.你欺骗了我，蟹老板
I wouldn't have collected
all those jellyfish had
我不会收集
所有那些水母都有
I known that this
.was their fate
我知道这
.是他们的命运
!This isn't right
！这是不对的
Jellyfish need wide-open
.space and fresh air
水母需要敞开
.空间和新鲜空气
.Easy, boy-
.简单点，男孩-
?What are you doing with that
？你用它做什么
Something that should have
!been done a long time ago
应该有的东西
！很久以前就完成了
!Noooo-
！不——
The squeaky bolt on this-
.door was driving me crazy
吱吱作响的螺栓-
.door快把我逼疯了
.Whew-
.呼-
And now I'm going to-
!set these jellyfish free
现在我要-
！释放这些水母
.Well, you can't-
.好吧，你不能-
The door is voice
activated, and it
门是声音
激活，并且它
.will only open if I say open
.仅当我说打开时才会打开
[LOUD BUZZING]
[大声的嗡嗡声]
!Freedom
！自由
!You'll never catch me-
！你永远抓不到我-
?What
？什么
!Blasted exercise craze
！爆炸的运动热潮
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
!Goodbye, friends-
！再见，朋友们-
.I'm taking jelly off the menu-
.我要把果冻从菜单上去掉-
He really got-
!burned on that deal
他真的得到了——
！因这笔交易而被烧毁
LAUGHING] All is]
.as it should be
笑]一切都是]
.理应如此
I promise never to use this
net for anything but pure sport
我保证永远不会使用这个
网络除了纯粹的运动之外什么都没有
.again
。再次
Jellyfish aren't meant
.to be captured forever
水母的意思不是
.永远被捕获
!Oh No-Name
！哦，无名
.I guess I can name you now
.我想我现在可以叫出你的名字了
.I'll call you Friend
.我会叫你朋友
[NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
[紧张的笑声]
ANNOUNCER: Welcome, sports
fans, to the 21st annual Bikini
播音员：欢迎，体育运动
粉丝们，第21届比基尼年度盛会
!Bottom Fry Cook Games
！底煎厨师游戏
[FLOURISH]
[繁荣]
I declare these-
!Fry Cook Games open
我宣布这些——
！油炸厨师游戏开放
[BEEP]
[嘟]
[FLOURISH]
[繁荣]
I declare these-
!Fry Cook Games open
我宣布这些——
！油炸厨师游戏开放
[EXPLOSION]
[爆炸]
!CROWD: Oh
！人群：哦
ANNOUNCER: So begin the
.21st Fry Cook Games
播音员：那么开始吧
.21届油炸厨师比赛
,I'm a realistic fish head
and it's a beautiful day here
,我是现实的鱼头
这是美好的一天
at Bikini Bottoms'
.Fast Food Coliseum
在比基尼泳裤'
.快餐体育馆
They come from everywhere
,microwaves hum, patties sizzle
他们来自四面八方
，微波炉嗡嗡作响，肉饼发出嘶嘶声
and heat lamps keep the fast
.food spirit warm and soggy
和加热灯保持快速
.食物精神温暖而湿润
But the real story
is the bitter rivalry
但真实的故事
是激烈的竞争
between former competitors
Mr. Krabs of The Krusty Krab
前竞争对手之间
蟹堡王的蟹先生
.and Plankton of the Chum Bucket
.和密友桶中的浮游生物
Who could forget
the year Mr. Krabs
谁能忘记
蟹老板那一年
a gold for this
?500-pickle clean-and-jerk
为此获得金牌
?500 次腌渍挺举
.Not Plankton
.不是浮游生物
Or when Plankton won
the hearts of millions
或者当浮游生物获胜时
数百万人的心
by performing this
perfect onion-ring routine
通过执行此操作
完美的洋葱圈常规
?with a broken antenna
？天线损坏
[GRUNTING]
[咕噜声]
.Krabs wasn't moved
.螃蟹不为所动
[SPITTING]
[随地吐痰]
And now late word is that-
this year, the Krusty Krab
现在迟来的消息是——
今年，蟹堡王
will be represented by a new
competitor on what is perhaps
将由一个新的代表
竞争对手可能是什么
the greatest day
.of his young life
最伟大的一天
.他年轻的生命
This is perhaps the greatest-
,day of my young like
这或许是最伟大的——
，我年轻时喜欢的日子
Mr. Krabs. [PANTING] I can't
believe I'm representing
蟹老板。 [气喘吁吁]我不能
相信我代表
the Krusty Krab in
.the Fry Cook Games
蟹堡王 (Krusty Krab)
.油炸厨师游戏
To bring home the
gold is to bring
为了带回家
黄金是要带来
honour and glory
.to the Krusty Krab
荣誉与荣耀
.到蟹堡王
And all that free publicity-
.will bring in customers
还有所有这些免费宣传——
.将带来客户
.So don't lose
.所以不要输
!Aye, aye, Mr. Krabs-
！是啊，是啊，蟹老板——
!Krusty Krab
!蟹堡王
--Krusty Crab
——脆皮蟹
.Hey, SpongeBob-
.嘿，海绵宝宝-
.Hi, Patrick-
.嗨，帕特里克-
!Krusty Krab
!蟹堡王
[Krusty Krab-- [GRUNTING
[蟹堡王--[咕噜声]
Are you trying to-
?move the ground
你是否想——
?移动地面
.You'll never move it like that
.你永远不会那样移动它
!You got to get underneath it
！你必须钻到它下面
.Come on, Patrick-
.来吧，帕特里克-
I'm trying to train
.for the games
我正在努力训练
.对于游戏
?Games-
?游戏-
?Can I play
？我可以玩吗
.Aw, sorry, Patrick-
.噢，对不起，帕特里克-
.You have to be a fry cook
.你必须是一名炒菜厨师
?Be a fry cook-
?当一名炒菜厨师-
?Is that all I gotta do
？这就是我要做的一切
.That'll be easy
.那会很容易
?What do you mean, easy-
？你是什么意思，简单-
?How hard could it be-
？这有多难-
They don't let just-
.anybody be a fry cook
他们不让——
.任何人都可以成为一名油炸厨师
.We're an elite corps
.我们是一支精英军团
.Doh, come on-
.Doh，来吧-
.You're just flipping patties
.你只是在翻转馅饼
!Hey-
！嘿-
Flipping is not as
.easy as it sounds
翻转并不像
.听起来很简单
[SIZZLE]-
[嘶嘶声]-
?Why don't you go home, Patrick-
？你为什么不回家，帕特里克-
You can complete in the laying
.under a rock all day games
您可以在铺设中完成
.在岩石下全天游戏
GASP] Well at least I]--
!don't polish my fingernails
喘息]好吧，至少我]——
！别擦我的指甲
!GASP] You take that back]-
!喘息]你收回那句话]-
,Fingernails-
!fingernails, fingernails
,指甲-
！指甲，指甲
You don't even-
!have fingernails
你甚至不-
！有指甲
I cannot believe-
!what I am hearing
我不敢相信——
!我所听到的
?How can you hear it-
？你怎么听得见——
!You don't have ears either
！你也没有耳朵
!FRUSTRATED) Holes)-
！沮丧）洞）-
!Holes
！洞
!Cone head-
!锥头-
!Yellow-
！黄色的-
!Pink-
！粉色的-
I'm going to get a job as a-
!fry cook, and it will be easy
我要找一份工作——
！炒一炒，就简单了
!Fine-
！美好的-
[GRUNTING]
[咕噜声]
!Krusty Krab
!蟹堡王
SNIFFING] What's]--
?that smell in the air
嗅探]什么是]--
？空气中的味道
!I spell Plankton
！我拼写浮游生物
?Oh yeah-
？哦是的-
[Well I smell-- [SNIFFING
.Phew, he's right
[嗯，我闻到了——[嗅
.唷，他是对的
.I love messing things up-
.我喜欢把事情搞砸-
Are you ready to-
?do or die, Krabs
你准备好了吗——
？要么做，要么死，蟹蟹
,Always ready-
.Plankton, always ready
,时刻准备着-
.浮游生物，时刻准备着
.Mmm good-
.嗯好-
Because today the Chum Bucket
.is going to kick your carapus
因为今天的密友桶
.会踢你的甲壳
.That's what you think-
.这就是你的想法-
.But I got me a champion
.但我得到了冠军
.SpongeBob, show him
.海绵宝宝，给他看看
.Look at him-
.看看他-
.In his prime
.在他的巅峰时期
!You ain't got no chance
！你没有机会
That's where-
.you're wrong, Krabs
那就是——
.你错了，蟹蟹
For I too have
因为我也有
.a champion
.冠军
,Ladies and gentlemen-
turn your attention
,女士们先生们-
转移你的注意力
.to the southwest corridor
.到西南走廊
Other way, (UNDER
.BREATH) imbeciles
其他方式，（下
.BREATH) 低能儿
!And stop
！然后停下来
!Perfect
！完美的
,Representing the Chum Bucket
,a creature so fearsome
,代表密友桶
,一个如此可怕的生物
so terrible, so mind-bendingly
large that those of you
如此可怕，如此令人费解
比你们这些人大
with weak constitutions may
.want to leave the stadium
体质较弱的人可能
.想要离开体育场
!I got to get out of here-
！我必须离开这里-
!Too late-
！为时已晚-
.Ready or not, here he comes
.无论准备好与否，他来了
,Quake with fear
!you mortal fools
, 恐惧得发抖
！你们这些凡人的傻瓜
Bow down before the
--awesome might of
面前跪拜
--令人敬畏的力量
[EXPLOSION]
[爆炸]
This huge guy was carrying the
!real contestant, Patrick Star
这个巨大的家伙背负着
！真正的参赛者，帕特里克·斯塔
Patrick, what are-
?you doing here
帕特里克，什么是——
？你在这里做什么
.You're not a fry cook
.你不是个炒菜的厨师
.Oh yes I am, Mr-
.SpongeBob SuperiorPants
.哦，是的，我是，先生-
.海绵宝宝高级裤
.Check it out
。一探究竟
I've been working for the Chum
.Bucket for almost five minutes
我一直在为密友工作
.桶大约五分钟
Well it doesn't matter-
anyway, because you're
好吧，没关系-
无论如何，因为你是
.going eat my dust
.去吃我的灰尘
.Nuh uh
.努呃呃
.I'm eating my own dust
.我正在吃自己的灰尘
!Not if I eat it first-
！如果我先吃它就不会-
Yellow-
黄色的-
!Pink-
！粉色的-
.I can't believe it, Mr. Krabs
.我简直不敢相信，蟹老板
.I thought Patrick was my friend
.我以为帕特里克是我的朋友
?Friend-
？朋友-
.Not in here, he ain't
.不在这里，他不在这里
?What do you mean-
？你是什么意思-
.He's not really your friend-
.他并不是真正的你的朋友-
?He's not-
？他不是——
He's plotting your-
.downfall right now
他正在密谋你的——
.现在的垮台
?He is-
？他是——
He's going to stab-
.you in the back
他要刺——
.后面的你
!He wouldn't
！他不会
.Of course he would
.他当然会
.Just look at him
.只要看着他
.Square, the shape of evil
.方形，邪恶的形状
He's making a mockery-
.of your profession
他在嘲讽——
.你的职业
Are we going to let
some pretender take away
我们要让
一些伪装者拿走了
?what belongs to the Krusty Krab
?什么属于蟹堡王
!No
！不
.Then get mean
.然后变得卑鄙
.I'm mean-
.我很刻薄-
.Get angry
。生气
!SHOUTING) I'm angry)-
！喊）我很生气）-
Now get out there-
.and win that meadow
现在出去-
.并赢得那片草地
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.Aaaah-
.啊啊啊-
ANNOUNCER: For our first
.event, the deep fry pole vault
播音员：我们的第一个
.事件，油炸撑竿跳高
Win this one for-
.the Krusty Krab
赢得这一场——
.蟹堡王
!For the Krusty Krab-
!对于蟹堡来说-
[SPLAT]
[啪]
!CROWD: Oh
！人群：哦
!Yea
！是的
[CHEERING]
[欢呼]
Win this one because-
.I told you to
赢得这一局是因为——
.我告诉过你
!Because you told me too-
！因为你也告诉过我——
[GRUNTING]
[咕噜声]
!Fish sticks-
!鱼条-
!Get your fish sticks here
！把你的鱼棒拿过来吧
--ANNOUNCER: The next event
.the chocolate high dive
--播音员：下一个活动
.巧克力高空跳水
Make way for the real-
.fry cook, Patrick
为真正的让路
.油炸厨师，帕特里克
ANNOUNCER: For his
dive, SpongeBob
播音员：为了他的
潜水, 海绵宝宝
will be attempting a full banana
.fudge pop with two sticks
将尝试吃完整的香蕉
.用两根棍子做软糖汽水
.And now, absolute silence
.现在，绝对的寂静
[DRUM ROLL]
[鼓声]
SCREAMING) I)-
!scream for ice cream
尖叫）我）-
！尖叫着要冰淇淋
!ANNOUNCER: Perfect entry
!播音员：完美入场
--And toasted almonds
.that's unexpected
--还有烤杏仁
.这是出乎意料的
!He stuck it
！他卡住了
And just look at
.that even coating
看看
.均匀的涂层
[SQUEAKING]
[吱吱声]
.Top that, Pinky-
.最重要的是，Pinky-
!Almonds-
！杏仁-
.Curse him, that's good
.咒骂他就好了
But perhaps a bit too
.highbrow for this crowd
但也许有点太
.对这群人来说是高雅的
He thinks he's
--better than them
他认为他是
——比他们更好
[GASPING]-
[喘气]-
!Better than you-
！比你更好-
[GASPING]-
[喘气]-
Now get up there and show-
him how the common man
现在站起来展示——
他多么普通人
prepares his frozen
!dairy traits
准备他的冷冻
!乳制品特性
[ROARING]-
[咆哮]-
ANNOUNCER: Patrick will be
--resurrecting an old favourite
播音员：帕特里克将
——复活一个旧的最爱
the single scoop strawberry
.cone with a chocolate dip
单勺草莓
.巧克力酱蛋筒
[CREAKING]
[吱吱作响]
!Just look at that concentration
！看看那个浓度
Oh, a little shaky
.on that entry
哦，有点摇摇欲坠
.在该条目上
!But just look at that form
！但只要看看那个表格
.Take that, Yellow Bow-
.拿着那个，黄弓-
.Laugh while you can, Pinky-
.尽情地笑吧，Pinky-
.It's not over yet
.还没结束
.That's what you think-
.这就是你的想法-
.But it's not over yet
.但事情还没有结束
.It's not over yet-
.还没结束-
With the score tied, we go
to our final event-- thumb
比分打平后，我们出发
我们的最后一个活动——拇指
.wrestling
。摔角
?Who will take home the gold
?谁将把金牌带回家
--Mr. Krabs of the Krusty Krab
- 先生。蟹堡蟹中的螃蟹
Don't forget-- he-
.called ye Yellow
别忘了——他——
.叫叶黄
[GNASHING TEETH]-
[咬牙切齿]-
ANNOUNCER: Or Plankton
?of the Chum Bucket
播音员：或者浮游生物
? 密友桶的
Don't forget, he-
!called you Pink
别忘了，他——
！叫你粉红
[GROWLING]
[咆哮]
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
[DING]
[叮]
[SCREAMING AND ROARING]
[尖叫和咆哮]
.Worked at the Chum Bucket-
.在 Chum Bucket 工作过-
.This is personal
.这是个人的
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
!SCREAMING) No)-
！尖叫）不）-
!My name's not Rick
！我的名字不是瑞克
[POUNDING AND YELLING]
[敲打和喊叫]
.I don't like idea you-
.我不喜欢你的想法-
.I don't like you more-
.我不再喜欢你了-
.I never liked you-
.我从来没有喜欢过你-
I a thousand times-
.never liked you
我一千次——
.从来没有喜欢过你
!Pink-
！粉色的-
!Yellow-
！黄色的-
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[咕哝和呻吟]
[RIPPING FABRIC]
[撕裂布料]
[GASPING]
[喘气]
?SPONGEBOB: Yellow
?海绵宝宝：黄色
?PATRICK: Pink
?帕特里克：粉红色
.You do care-
.你确实关心-
[SOBBING]
[抽泣]
Let's promise never-
.to fight again, buddy
让我们承诺永远——
.再次战斗，伙计
.Yeah, pal-
.是的，朋友-
.Let's go home
.我们回家吧
[WHISTLING]-
[口哨声]-
[BOOING]
[嘘声]
!Hey-
！嘿-
?Where you going
?你要去哪里
Get back here and
!kill each other
回到这里然后
！互相残杀
PATRICK: You're my
.best friend ever
帕特里克：你是我的
.有史以来最好的朋友
.SPONGEBOB: You too, Patrick
.海绵宝宝：你也是，帕特里克
PATRICK: You know, these were
.white when I bought them
帕特里克：你知道，这些是
.white 当我买的时候
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]